// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single

export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Java, Javascript and DevOps',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question:
          'What type of problems do you enjoy solving the most?',
        choices: [
          'Complex algorithms and data structures', 
          'User interface and interactivity', 
          'System performance and scalability'],
        type: 'Javascript',
        correctAnswer: ' ',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question:
          'What kind of projects do you enjoy working on?',
        choices: [
          'Backend systems and applications', 
          'Frontend web development', 
          'Infrastructure management and automation'],
        type: 'Javascript',
        correctAnswer: '',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question:
          'Which of the following programming languages do you prefer the most?',
        choices: [
          'Java',
          'Javascript',
          'Bash or Python'
        ],
        type: 'Javascript',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is your preferred development environment?',
        choices: ['IntelliJ IDEA', 'Visual Studio Code', 'Vim or Emacs'],
        type: 'Javascript',
        correctAnswer: 'const',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'How do you prefer to debug your code?',
        choices: [
          'Using a debugger and stepping through the code', 
          'Using console.log statements', 
          'Using log analysis and monitoring tools' 
          ],
        type: 'Javascript',
        correctAnswer: 'Web browser',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'How important is security in your development process?',
        choices: ['Very important', 'Somewhat important', 'Not very important'],
        type: 'Java',
        correctAnswer: 'Compilation',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'How do you prefer to deploy your code?',
        choices: [
          'Using a continuous integration and deployment (CI/CD) pipeline', 
          'Manually deploying the code', 
          'Using containerization and orchestration tools'
          ],
        type: 'Java',
        correctAnswer: '.java',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'How comfortable are you with Linux command line tools?',
        choices: ['Very comfortable', 'Somewhat comfortable', 'Not comfortable'],
        type: 'Java',
        correctAnswer: 'Use of pointers',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'How do you stay up to date with the latest technologies and trends?',
        choices: [
          'Reading technical books and articles', 
          'Attending conferences and meetups', 
          'Experimenting with new tools and technologies' 
          ],
        type: 'Java',
        correctAnswer: 'JDK',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What motivates you most in your work?',
        choices: [
          'Solving challenging technical problems', 
          'Building great user experiences', 
          'Improving system reliability and performance', 
          ],
        type: 'Java',
        correctAnswer: '.class',
      },
    ],
  }

  